Lowell Thomas Jr.
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Lowell Thomas Jr., 2.1.3.3.4
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Tay Thomas, Jr. (passport photographs), 1953; 4 (Box 1530)
    - [Mary Taylor], 1
    - [Mary Taylor], 2
    - [LT Jr.], 3
    - [LT Jr.], 4
    - [LT Jr.], 5
    - [LT Jr.], 6
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. with Thomas E. Dewey, undated; 5 (Box 1530)
    - [LT Jr. with Thomas E. Dewey], 1
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. with Jim Thorpe, 1941; 6 (Box 1530)
    - Caption: Lowell Thomas Jr. and Jim Thorpe, famous Indian athlete. 7/7/41, 1
    - Verso: Lowell Jr. + Jim Thorpe, the famous Indian athlete. Fifteen years in the Welfare Office in Cripple Creek, above my desk - Mrs. A.W. Oliver, Thought your granddaughter might like it, Lowell Sr., 1-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Dogs, 1920s - 1940; 7 (Box 1530)
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 1
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 2
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 3
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 4
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 5
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 6
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 7
    - Sonny [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 8
    - Verso: Sonny, 8-verso
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 9
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog, holding football], 10
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 11
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog] 2, 12
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 13
    - Sonny + Bozo [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 14
    - Verso: Sonny + Bozo, 14-verso
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 15
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 16
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 17
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 18
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], [3 copies], 19
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 20
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Knickerbocker Greys, circa 1930s; 8 (Box 1530)
    - [Painting of LT Jr.], [2 copies], 1
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog], 2
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog]Oct 15, 3
    - [Young LT Jr. with a dog] [2 copies], 4
    - [Young LT and other boys in uniform], 5
    - Verso: Gen. Somervell; 2nd U.S.A. Commander in W.W.I. - Col. L.T., Jr. on right, 5-verso
    - [LT Jr. in uniform], 6
    - [LT Jr. in uniform], 7
    - [LT Jr. in uniform], 8
    - [LT Jr. in uniform], 9
    - [LT Jr. in uniform], 10
    - [LT Jr. in uniform], 11
    - [LT Jr. in uniform], 12
    - [LT Jr. in uniform], 13
    - [LT Jr. and another boy in uniform], 14
    - [LT Jr. and another boy in uniform], 15
    - [Presentation of young men in uniform - rifle drill team], 16
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Miscellaneous photographs, undated; 9 (Box 1530)
    - [sign for Earthquate Park in Anchorage, Alaska], 1
    - [aerial photo], 2
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Photographs to be placed in scrapbook, undated; 10 (Box 1530)
    - [Man], 1
    - [Two women and a man drinking tea on a porch], 2
    - [Two men with ropes], 3
    - [Man on a horse, backwards], 4
    - [Man], 5
    - [View of snowy mountainside], 6
    - [View of snowy rooftops and mountainside], 7
    - [View of snowy mountainside], 8
    - [View of snowy rooftops and mountainside], 9
    - [Man], 10
    - [Man with rope], 11
    - [Man], 12
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Army Air Force scrapbook photographs [includes visit by Lowell Thomas to the pre-flight school for pilots at Maxwell field], 1943; 11 (Box 1530)
    - [LT Jr. and other men on a plastic horse and carriage], 1
    - Note: [envelope], 2
    - [LT Jr. and other men on a plastic horse and carriage], 3
    - "Ready to try their wings" - this group of 230 Army Aviation Cadets from the Boston Aviation Cadet Examining Board is due to "take off" for pre-flight training at Nashville, Tenn. Today. In front are Major Edward H. Holterman, left, Army Air Corps, and Ralph H. Welles, Army Medical Corps, 4
    - Note: "Ready to try their wings" - this group of 230 Army Aviation Cadets from the Boston Aviation Cadet Examining Board is due to "take off" for pre-flight training at Nashville, Tenn. Today. In front are Major Edward H. Holterman, left, Army Air Corps, and Ralph H. Welles, Army Medical Corps, 5
    - [Aviation cadets], 6
    - [Maj-Gen Royce, Col. Elmer J. Bowling, Commanding Officer, Maxwell Field [Lowell Thomas at the microphone], 7
    - [Maj-Gen Royce, Col. Elmer J. Bowling, Commanding Officer, Maxwell Field [Lowell Thomas at the microphone], 8
    - Verso: Maj-Gen Royce, Col. Elmer J. Bowling, Commanding Officer, Maxwell Field, 8-verso
    - Newspaper clipping: "Maxwell's Cadets Hear Surprise Talk By Lowell Thomas, 9
    - Col. Louis A. Guenther, Asst. C.O. Pre-flight School and Director of Training for Maxwell Field, Mr. Lowell Thomas, Capt. B. C. Pope, Jr., Public Relations Officer, Maxwell Field, 3/29/43, 10
    - Verso: Col. Louis A. Guenther, Asst. C.O. Pre-flight School and Director of Training for Maxwell Field, Mr. Lowell Thomas, Capt. B. C. Pope, Jr., Public Relations Officer, Maxwell Field, 3/29/43, 10-verso
    - Cadet mess hall [Lowell Thomas receiving food], 11
    - Verso: Cadet mess hall, 11-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas seated with officer], 12
    - L. Thomas [Lowell Thomas seated with officer at resturant table], 13
    - Verso: L. Thomas, 13-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Politics (campaigning for Congress), circa 1962; 12 (Box 1530)
    - [Photograph of Lowell Thomas, Jr.'s campaign headquarters], 1
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Politics (Lowell Thomas campaigning for Lowell Thomas, Jr. in his bid to become Lieutenant Governor of Alaska) [color photographs], 1974; 13 (Box 1530)
    - [Man and woman posing for photograph], 1
    - [Palmer, AK; Primary Campaign, 1974], 2
    - Verso: Palmer, AK; primary campaign, 1974, 2-verso
    - Note: [envelope], 3
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Politics (Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Jay S. Hammond sworn in as Lieutenant Governor and Governor of Alaska), 1975 January 18; 14 (Box 1530)
    - [Governor(?) getting sworn in], 1
    - [Governors(?) shaking hands, 2
    - [Group of people at governor's office], 3
    - [Governor(?) getting sworn in], 4
    - [Man speaking at microphone], 5
    - [New governor(?) speaking at podium], 6
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Iran, circa 1948; 15 (Box 1530)
    - Aerial view of Tehran, 1
    - Verso: Aerial view of Tehran, 1-verso
    - A mosque at Isfahan, 2
    - Verso: A mosque at Isfahan, 2-verso
    - A mosque at Isfahan, 3
    - Verso: A mosque at Isfahan, 3-verso
    - Ruins at Persepolis, 4
    - Verso: Ruins at Persepolis, 4-verso
    - Iran's highest, Mr. Demavend [Mount Demavand], 5
    - Verso: Iran's highest, Mr. Demavend [Mount Demavand], 5-verso
    - Rug making, 6
    - Verso: Rug making, 6-verso
    - Cleaning new rugs at Isfahan, 7
    - Verso: Cleaning new rugs at Isfahan, 7-verso
    - Women working on a loom, 8
    - Verso: Women working on a loom, 8-verso
    - Inside a Persian textile factory, 9
    - Verso: Inside a Persian textile factory, 9-verso
    - Inside a Persian textile factory, women workers, 10
    - Verso: Inside a Persian textile factory, women workers, 10-verso
    - Same as seven [Cleaning new rugs at Isfahan], 11
    - Verso: Same as seven [Cleaning new rugs at Isfahan], 11-verso
    - Child labor at loom, 12
    - Verso: Child labor at loom, 12-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 13
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 13-verso
    - Women and children in match factory, 14
    - Verso: Women and children in match factory, 14-verso
    - Same [Women and children in match factory], 15
    - Verso: Same [Women and children in match factory], 15-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] with Franc Shor in Isfahan, 16
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] with Franc Shor in Isfahan, 16-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 17
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 17-verso
    - Bahktiari dance, 18
    - Veros: Bahktiari dance, 18-verso
    - Stick dance, 19
    - Verso: Stick dance, 19-verso
    - Majid Khan, of the Bahktiari, WOD's [William O. Douglas] host, 20
    - Verso: Majid Khan, of the Bahktiari, WOD's [William O. Douglas] host, 20-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 21
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 21-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 22
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 22-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 23
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 23-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 24
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 24-verso
    - Bahktiari women, 25
    - Verso: Bahktiari women, 25-verso
    - Bahktiari women, 26
    - Verso: Bahktiari women, 26-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] with Lowell Thomas, Jr.; Persian friend in background, 27
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] with Lowell Thomas, Jr.; Persian friend in background, 27-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] with Lowell Thomas, Jr.; Persian friend in background, 28
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] with Lowell Thomas, Jr.; Persian friend in background, 28-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 29
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 29-verso
    - WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 30
    - Verso: WOD [William O. Douglas] can best identify, 30-verso
    - Jimmy Motarjemi, 31
    - Jimmy Motarjemi, 32
    - Note: physical note containing captions for photographs 1-30, 33
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Ahmet Sayin (Turkey), 1948; 16 (Box 1530)
    - Note: Letter from Ahmet Sayin: Dear Mr. Thomas, Please excuse my being late to write to you as it has been difficult for me to find somebody to translate my letter into English. I am sendig you three photographs as a souvenir of our friendship during your short stay in our country. Hoping that your keeping well and I shall hear from you soon, I remain, Sincerely yours, [signed] A. Sayin, 1
    - [LT Jr. and another man looking in the hood of a car], 2
    - [LT Jr. and another man on a muddy road], 3
    - [LT Jr. and two other men posing for a photograph], 4
    - A view of Ordu - Turkey, 5
    - Verso: A view of Ordu - Turkey, 5-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: United States Navy's goodwill tour of South America with photographer Bonney Powell and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1939; 17 (Box 1530)
    - [Plaque about the U.S. Cruiser San Francisco], 1
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas deplaning at Cuba], 2
    - [LT Jr.(?) posing on a ship], 3
    - [Note: Lowell Thomas, Jr. age fifteen on board the U.S.S. San Francisco - heavy cruiser. Assisant cameraman on U. S. Navy good will cruise around South America], 4
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr., 5
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr., 5-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. at Montevideo, Uruguay], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Bonney Powell], 9
    - Mask as shown on margin bottom + one side [?], 10
    - Verso: Mask as shown on margin bottom + one side [?], 10-verso
    - Bonney Powell of Fox Movietone. Taken aboard the U.S.S. San Francisco while mooring in Montevideo, Uruguay, 11
    - Verso: Bonney Powell of Fox Movietone. Taken aboard the U.S.S. San Francisco while mooring in Montevideo, Uruguay, 11-verso
    - Bonney Powell with the Tuscaloosa and Quincy in the back-ground, 12
    - Verso: Bonney Powell with the Tuscaloosa and Quincy in the back-ground, 12-verso
    - [Bonney Powell with the Tuscaloosa and Quincy in the back-ground], 13
    - Lieut. Commander Hyman and Bonney Powell. Commander Hyman played the role of Davy Jones during the Neptune ceremony, 14
    - Verso: Lieut. Commander Hyman and Bonney Powell. Commander Hyman played the role of Davy Jones during the Neptune ceremony, 14-verso
    - Verso: Lieut. Cmd. Hyman and Bonney Powell again, 15
    - Verso: Verso: Lieut. Cmd. Hyman and Bonney Powell again, 15-verso
    - Bonney Powell and Lieut. Bond buying some bananas at a little town in the Andes, 16
    - Verso: LBonney Powell and Lieut. Bond buying some bananas at a little town in the Andes, 16-verso
    - Bonney and his American friend who is visiting in Venezuela, 17
    - Verso: Bonney and his American friend who is visiting in Venezuela, 17-verso
    - Bonney Powell and a lady friend taking pictures of the poor peoples' homes in Caracas, 18
    - Verso: Bonney Powell and a lady friend taking pictures of the poor peoples' homes in Caracas, 18-verso
    - Looking down upon the city of Caracas, Venezuela, 19
    - Verso:Looking down upon the city of Caracas, Venezuela, 19-verso
    - A candid shot of Ensigns Ed Manown and Red Johnson, 20
    - Verso: A candid shot of Ensigns Ed Manown and Red Johnson, 20-verso
    - The Tuscaloosa and Quincy berthed at Montevideo, 21
    - Verso: The Tuscaloosa and Quincy berthed at Montevideo, 21-verso
    - The Tuscaloosa and Quincy tied up at Montevideo, 22
    - Verso: The Tuscaloosa and Quincy tied up at Montevideo, 22-verso
    - [The Tuscaloosa and Quincy berthed at Montevideo], 23
    - The U.S.S. Quincy coming alongside the Tuscaloosa in Montevideo, 24
    - Verso: The U.S.S. Quincy coming alongside the Tuscaloosa in Montevideo, 24-verso
    - [The U.S.S. Quincy(?)], 25
    - Looking aft at the Quincy and Tuscaloosa which is hidden behind the airplane hoist, 26
    - Verso:Looking aft at the Quincy and Tuscaloosa which is hidden behind the airplane hoist, 26-verso
    - [The Tuscaloosa(?)], 27
    - [The Tuscaloosa(?)], 28
    - The Quincy, 29
    - Verso: The Quincy, 29-verso
    - Another shot of the Quincy, 30
    - Verso: Another shot of the Quincy, 30-verso
    - Looking down on the U.S.S. Quincy's stern from the machine-gun platform. You can see turrets No. 1 at the bottom. Those are eight inch guns with a range of about twenty miles or more, 31
    - Verso: Looking down on the U.S.S. Quincy's stern from the machine-gun platform. You can see turrets No. 1 at the bottom. Those are eight inch guns with a range of about twenty miles or more, 31-verso
    - Ensign Rogers in the wheel-house of the U.S.S. San Francisco, 32
    - Verso: Ensign Rogers in the wheel-house of the U.S.S. San Francisco, 32-verso
    - Visitors day aboard the U.S.S. San Francisco in Montevideo, 33
    - Verso: Visitors day aboard the U.S.S. San Francisco in Montevideo, 33-verso
    - Looking out my port-hole at the other cruisers, 34
    - Verso: Looking out my port-hole at the other cruisers, 34-verso
    - [Looking out the port-hole at the other cruisers], 35
  Box 1531
- Lowell Thomas Jr., 2.1.3.3.4
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: United States Navy's goodwill tour of South America with photographer Bonney Powell and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1939; 1 (Box 1531)
    - [Members of the crew bathing in the sun], 1
    - Members of the crew bathing in the tropical sun on the fan-tail [3 copies], 2
    - Verso: Members of the crew bathing in the tropical sun on the fan-tail, 2-verso
    - Hard at work on the after hatch [2 copies], 3
    - Verso: Hard at work on the after hatch, 3-verso
    - Splicing rope for a cargo net [2 copies], 4
    - Verso: Splicing rope for a cargo net, 4-verso
    - Worshipping the Jolly Roger during the Neptune ceremonies [2 copies], 5
    - Verso: Worshipping the Jolly Roger during the Neptune ceremonies, 5-verso
    - Another pollywog bites the dust for Neptune Rex, 6
    - Verso: Another pollywog bites the dust for Neptune Rex, 6-verso
    - Another scene of the ducking. After the tank a man gets a pretty stiff paddling and then becomes a shellback, 7
    - Verso: Another scene of the ducking. After the tank a man gets a pretty stiff paddling and then becomes a shellback, 7-verso
    - [Another scene of the ducking], 8
    - "Bears" - Shellbacks - Who give the royal duckings, putting a man through the tank, 9
    - Verso: "Bears" - Shellbacks - Who give the royal duckings, putting a man through the tank, 9-verso
    - The President of Uruguay coming on board the U.S.S. San Francisco at Montevideo, 10
    - Verso: The President of Uruguay coming on board the U.S.S. San Francisco at Montevideo, 10-verso
    - The President of Uruguay and Admiral Kimmel, 11
    - Verso: The President of Uruguay and Admiral Kimmel, 11-verso
    - Looking aft from the Flag Bridge, Montevideo, 12
    - Verso: Looking aft from the Flag Bridge, Montevideo, 12-verso
    - The U.S.S. Quincy during rough weather. Taken from inside our hangar [2 copies], 13
    - Verso: The U.S.S. Quincy during rough weather. Taken from inside our hangar, 13-verso
    - Down she goes!, 14
    - Verso: Down she goes!, 14-verso
    - Quincy, near. Tuscaloosa, distant., 15
    - Verso: Quincy, near. Tuscaloosa, distant., 15-verso
    - The Tuscaloosa, in the background, is coming up like a submarine, 16
    - Verso: The Tuscaloosa, in the background, is coming up like a submarine, 16-verso
    - Quincy, near. Tuscaloosa, distant, 17
    - Verso: Quincy, near. Tuscaloosa, distant, 17-verso
    - The Quincy going under, and the Tuscaloosa, 18
    - Verso: The Quincy going under, and the Tuscaloosa, 18-verso
    - The Quincy and Tuscaloosa bucking the seas [2 copies], 19
    - Verso: The Quincy and Tuscaloosa bucking the seas, 19-verso
    - [The Quincy and Tuscaloosa bucking the seas], 20
    - Quincy, near. Tuscaloosa, distant. [2 copies], 21
    - Verso: Quincy, near. Tuscaloosa, distant., 21-verso
    - [View of the Quincy(?)] [2 copies], 22
    - The U.S.S. Quincy and Tuscaloosa, 23
    - Verso: The U.S.S. Quincy and Tuscaloosa, 23-verso
    - The U.S.S. Quincy, 24
    - Verso: The U.S.S. Quincy, 24-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: United States Navy's goodwill tour of South America with photographer Bonney Powell and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1939; 2 (Box 1531)
    - [View of a ship], 1
    - Lieut. Willis Fortune coming alongside in one of our four scouting planes, 2
    - Verso: Lieut. Willis Fortune coming alongside in one of our four scouting planes, 2-verso
    - Taxying [sic] up to the ship after a flight at sea, 3
    - Verso: Taxying [sic] up to the ship after a flight at sea, 3-verso
    - Picking up an airplane while underway, 4
    - Verso: Picking up an airplane while underway, 4-verso
    - Heavy seas on our way from Buenos Aires to the Straits of Magellan. Taken from the San Francisco's bridge, showing the Quincy going under a big one, 5
    - Verso: Heavy seas on our way from Buenos Aires to the Straits of Magellan. Taken from the San Francisco's bridge, showing the Quincy going under a big one, 5-verso
    - Trying to take a hearing on Cape Virgins at the entrance to the Straits of Magellan. A hat would have helped a lot, 6
    - Verso: Trying to take a hearing on Cape Virgins at the entrance to the Straits of Magellan. A hat would have helped a lot, 6-verso
    - A cold bitter day as we approached the Straits, 7
    - Verso: A cold bitter day as we approached the Straits, 7-verso
    - Sunset in the Straits of Magellan. This picture was taken before we reached the treacherous narrows, 8
    - Verso: Sunset in the Straits of Magellan. This picture was taken before we reached the treacherous narrows, 8-verso
    - Punta Arenas in the Straits of Magellan where we took on a pilot, 9
    - Verso: Punta Arenas in the Straits of Magellan where we took on a pilot, 9-verso
    - [View of the ocean], 10
    - Looking over Bonney's shoulder at the foc'sle of the U.S.S. San Francisco, which in another second was completely submerged, 11
    - Verso: Looking over Bonney's shoulder at the foc'sle of the U.S.S. San Francisco, which in another second was completely submerged, 11-verso
    - [View from the ship], 12
    - [View of ships at dock], 13
    - [View from the ship], 14
    - [View from the ship], 15
    - [View from the ship], 16
    - [View from the ship], 17
    - [View from the ship], 18
    - [View from the ship], 19
    - [View from the ship], 20
    - A dredge in the river Plate, 21
    - Verso: A dredge in the river Plate, 21-verso
    - In Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 22
    - Verso: In Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 22-verso
    - A little town near Guantanamo, Cuba, 23
    - Verso: A little town near Guantanamo, Cuba, 23-verso
    - Playing the wheels in Cuba, 24
    - Verso: Playing the wheels in Cuba, 24-verso
    - Two Cuban boys, a piano and singer, playing in a saloon near Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 25
    - Verso: Two Cuban boys, a piano and singer, playing in a saloon near Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 25-verso
    - [Man playing a piano], 26
    - A Square in Buenos Aires, Argentina, 27
    - Verso: A Square in Buenos Aires, Argentina, 27-verso
    - A Venezuelan shoe shine boy, 28
    - Verso: A Venezuelan shoe shine boy, 28-verso
    - [A Venezuelan shoeshine boy], 29
    - Lieut. Blake in Caracas, 30
    - Verso: Lieut. Blake in Caracas, 30-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: United States Navy's goodwill tour of South America with photographer Bonney Powell and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1939; 3 (Box 1531)
    - Looking up a street in Valparaiso, Chile. Many of the city's people live in houses atop a high hill in the middle of Valparaiso, which you can see in the background, 1
    - Verso: Looking up a street in Valparaiso, Chile. Many of the city's people live in houses atop a high hill in the middle of Valparaiso, which you can see in the background, 1-verso
    - Lieut. Lair and Lieut. Fortune, who is one of the aviators on the San Francisco. Taken in Lima, Peru, 2
    - Verso: Lieut. Lair and Lieut. Fortune, who is one of the aviators on the San Francisco. Taken in Lima, Peru, 2-verso
    - Taken at another town in the Andes where a sailor and a marine are buying bananas from the native women, 3
    - Verso: Taken at another town in the Andes where a sailor and a marine are buying bananas from the native women, 3-verso
    - The foot of the Andes mountains, 4
    - Verso: The foot of the Andes mountains, 4-verso
    - The Andes from our train, 5
    - Verso: The Andes from our train, 5-verso
    - A town high up in the Andes. Taken from the train window as we climbed to Rio Blanco, 12000 feet high, 6
    - Verso: A town high up in the Andes. Taken from the train window as we climbed to Rio Blanco, 12000 feet high, 6-verso
    - An old Volcano in the Andes near Lima, 7
    - Verso: An old Volcano in the Andes near Lima, 7-verso
    - The top of the world, 8
    - Verso: The top of the world, 8-verso
    - Lieut. Bond during the train ride into the mountains, 9
    - Verso: Lieut. Bond during the train ride into the mountains, 9-verso
    - Ensign Peter Green, 10
    - Verso: Ensign Peter Green, 10-verso
    - The sailors tried their best to ride the llamas at Rio Blanco in Andes, 11
    - Verso: The sailors tried their best to ride the llamas at Rio Blanco in Andes, 11-verso
    - [The sailors tried their best to ride the llamas at Rio Blanco in Andes], 12
    - [The sailors tried their best to ride the llamas at Rio Blanco in Andes], 13
    - [View of the Andes], 14
    - [View of the Andes], 15
    - [View of the Andes], 16
    - [View of the Andes], 17
    - [View of the Andes], 18
    - [View of the Andes], 19
    - [View of the Andes], 20
    - [View of the Andes], 21
    - Uniform prescribed for Lieut. Ernest Blake, USN., the Admiral's aid, who had not been across the "Line" before. He was forced to stand on the bow of the ship "reporting" everything he saw and the progress of King Neptune etc. for some two hours. Lieut. Blake is to the left a sailor to the right in picture, 22
    - Verso: Uniform prescribed for Lieut. Ernest Blake, USN., the Admiral's aid, who had not been across the "Line" before. He was forced to stand on the bow of the ship "reporting" everything he saw and the progress of King Neptune etc. for some two hours. Lieut. Blake is to the left a sailor to the right in picture, 22-verso
    - [Man], 23
    - [Man playing tuba], 24
    - [Two men posing for a photo], 25
    - [Man posing for a photo], 26
    - [Group of men uniform], 27
    - [Plane], 28
    - [Men boarding a plane], 29
    - [Men in uniform saluting], 30
    - [Two ships at sea], 31
    - [Group of men], 32